[
	{
		"Num":"1",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}\\frac{\\tan{x}}{\\cos{x}}dx=\\frac{ア\\sqrt{イ}-ウ}{エ}",
		"answer":"2333",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"2",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{2}}\\frac{dx}{\\sin{x}\\tan{x}}=アイ+\\sqrt{ウ}",
		"answer":"-12",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{2}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"3",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{\\sin{x}-\\cos{x}}{\\sin{2x}+1}dx=\\frac{\\sqrt{ア}-イ}{ウ}",
		"answer":"-222",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"4",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{\\tan{x}}{1-\\sin^2{x}}dx=\\frac{ア}{イ}",
		"answer":"12",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"5",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{8}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{dx}{\\sin^2{x}\\tan{x}}=ア+\\sqrt{イ}",
		"answer":"12",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{8}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"6",
		"question":"\\int_{2}^{4}\\frac{dx}{(x-a)(a-x)}=\\frac{ア}{(ア-a)(a-イ)}",
		"answer":"24",
		"int":"\\int_{2}^{4}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"7",
		"question":"\\int_{a+1}^{b+1}\\frac{(x-a)+(x-b)}{(x-a)^2\\cdot(x-b)^2}dx=\\frac{ア(イ-ウ)}{エ-(イ-ウ)^2}",
		"answer":"2ba1",
		"int":"\\int_{a+1}^{b+1}",
		"level":"2"
	},
	{
		"Num":"8",
		"question":"\\int_{e}^{e^2}\\frac{dx}{x(\\log{x})^2}=\\frac{ア}{イ}",
		"answer":"23",
		"int":"\\int_{e}^{e^2}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"9",
		"question":"\\int_{e}^{e^2}\\frac{dx}{x(\\log{x})^3}=\\frac{ア}{イ}",
		"answer":"38",
		"int":"\\int_{e}^{e^2}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"10",
		"question":"\\int_{\\log{2}}^{2\\log{2}}\\frac{dx}{e^x+e^{-x}-2}=\\frac{ア}{イ}",
		"answer":"23",
		"int":"\\int_{\\log{2}}^{2\\log{2}}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"1",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}\\frac{dx}{\\sin{x}}=ア\\log(イ\\sqrt{ウ}-エ)",
		"answer":"-233",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}",
		"level":"2"
	},
	{
		"Num":"2",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{dx}{\\cos{x}}=\\log(\\sqrt{ア}+イ)",
		"answer":"21",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"2"
	},
	{
		"Num":"3",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}\\frac{dx}{\\tan^2{x}}=\\frac{ア\\sqrt{イ}-ウ}{エ}",
		"answer":"43π6",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}",
		"level":"2"
	},
	{
		"Num":"4",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}\\frac{dx}{\\sin^3{x}}=\\frac{1}{ア}\\log{\\frac{イ\\sqrt{ウ}+エ}{ウ}}+\\sqrt{オ}-\\frac{1}{ウ}",
		"answer":"44373",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{3}}",
		"level":"4"
	},
	{
		"Num":"5",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{dx}{\\cos^3{x}}=-\\frac{1}{ア}\\log(イ-ウ\\sqrt{エ})-\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{オ}}",
		"answer":"43222",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"4"
	},
	{
		"Num":"6",
		"question":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}\\frac{dx}{\\tan^3{x}}=ア-\\frac{イ}{ウ}\\log{エ}",
		"answer":"1122",
		"int":"\\int_{\\frac{\\pi}{6}}^{\\frac{\\pi}{4}}",
		"level":"2"
	},
	{
		"Num":"7",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}e^x\\sin{x}dx=\\frac{ア}{イ}(e^{ウ}+エ)",
		"answer":"12π1",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"8",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}e^x\\cos{x}dx=\\frac{アイ}{ウ}(e^{エ}+オ)",
		"answer":"-12π1",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"9",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}e^{-x}\\sin{x}dx=\\frac{ア}{イ}(e^{ウエ}+オ)",
		"answer":"12-π1",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}",
		"level":"1"
	},
	{
		"Num":"10",
		"question":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}e^{-x}\\cos{x}dx=\\frac{ア}{イ}(e^{ウエ}+オ)",
		"answer":"12-π1",
		"int":"\\int_{0}^{\\pi}",
		"level":"1"
	}
]
